hrwebdir.org 2016-11-06

# Human Ranked Directory - Privacy Policy

* * *

**Privacy Policy**

* * *

We, Human Ranked Web Directory (hrwebdir.org) respects your privacy and the information you send us, under no circumstances we will share your private information to other companies or third parties, unless we get explicit permission from our users. 

**Information we collect**

Since our main goal of this project to rank and accept high quality websites, we collect the following information from our users...

  * 1\. Title
  * 2\. Description
  * 3\. Keywords
  * 4\. Submitter name and Email
  * 5\. Reciprocal Link (if required)
  * 6\. IP Address (to prevent spamming and automatic submissions)

**Announcements and Offers**

We normally send email confirmation to our users, who submitted their sites for inclusion in our directory. This information will contain whether their submission is accepted or rejected and if accepted the editor will score the site and give a rank depending on various parameters on quality, content and relevance. 

We may get in directly in contact with our users by email, if needed or for any clarification is required. Occasionally we email our users special offers, newsletters and announcements.

**Public Information**

Since we are a directory listing many content rich and quality sites, we publish the following information in respective categories and the following are available to public and search engines. 

  * URL submitted
  * Title 
  * Description
  * Keywords
  * Scores and Ranking

**Advertising and Sponsors**

If necessary for promotion and marketing, we may share the following submitted information to third party advertisers and sponsors : URL, Title, Description, Keywords, Unique Visitors, Scores and Rankings. These information are usually non-personal information and does not include personal user data or email.

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

**Legal Requirements**

Though we make every effort to preserve our user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law so as to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal procedure. 

**Websites and External Links**

This site contains many external links to other websites, so we cannot be responsible for privacy policy of other external sites. 

**We encourage our users to check back our privacy policy frequently as it may change from time to time.**
